<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ankit</title>
    <link>https://nezubn.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ankit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://nezubn.com&#34;&gt;Ankit Sharma&lt;/a&gt; 2025</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nezubn.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Musings #3</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/posts/musings_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/posts/musings_3/</guid>
      <description>June is the most exciting month for me. Every year Apple organises its World Wide Developer Conference (WWDC) in June. I am a big Apple fan, been watching these since 2014 and now its almost 11 years and the level of excitement hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings #2</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/posts/musings_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/posts/musings_2/</guid>
      <description>Oh man, did I skip a beat or what? I had thought that I would be regular in writing these but I have been shit lately. Let&amp;rsquo;s forget what happened and give it a fresh start. From now on, biweekly musings are going out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings #1</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/posts/musings_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/posts/musings_1/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I have acquired this domain and thought about consistent writing. But, I kept procrastinating. I always felt what exactly should I write, and as I am queering my career in tech, I have plenty to express and write about now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Engineer&#39;s Musings</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/musings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/musings/</guid>
      <description>2025 Musings #3 Musings #2 Musings #1 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Everything I want but don&amp;rsquo;t have, and everything I have but don&amp;rsquo;t want, is because I lack knowledge.
“The cosmos is within us. We are made of star-stuff. We are a way for the universe to know itself.” ~ Carl Sagan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create new Google Doc from the search bar</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/posts/gdoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/posts/gdoc/</guid>
      <description>TIL, you can create new doc, sheet, slide, form, site or a calendar event from the search bar at the top of the Chrome. This is so convinient if you&amp;rsquo;re a Chrome user.
Create a new Google Doc: doc.new Create a new Google Sheet: sheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DFS?</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/posts/dfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/posts/dfs/</guid>
      <description>I have always struggled with Depth First Search, DFS. I now have started solving it using first principles and it has started to make sense.
DFS can be solved using two methods:
Recursive solution Iterative solution, using stacks To solve recursively we must keep few things in our mind:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to find good research papers?</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/posts/find-research-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/posts/find-research-papers/</guid>
      <description>There is plethora of research happening all around us and in the recent times the incoming number of research papers have increased by quite a number.
This raises a question on how to find a good paper and give it a read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/links/</guid>
      <description>My favorite links to some of the good posts i have read around the internet.
My links keeping up with ai Favorite links teach yourself programming in 10 years Patrick Collision | patrickc
advice fast bookshelf Paul Graham | paulg
How to do great work Fierce Nerds Great Hackers Some great blogs/articles Generic Invisible Details of Interactive Design How to become a hacker Extreme brainstorming questions to trigger new, better ideas Implementing Raft People Startups, Products &amp;amp; Strategy Balaji Srinivasan | balajis Paul Graham | paulg Aaron Swartz Vitalik Buterin | vitalikbuterin Naval | naval Software Engineering John Siracusa | siracusa Joel Spolsky | spolsky Karl Seguin | karlseguin Phil Eaton | eatonphil matklad Karl Seguin Machine Learning Andrej Karpathy | blog | karpathy Greg Brockman | gdb Yann LeCun | ylecun Jason Wei Lilian Weng </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/papershelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:06:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/papershelf/</guid>
      <description>The papers I am reading and I recommend. The list contains papers extensively from the fields of Physics, Machine Learning / Deep Learning and Software Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The AI Summer</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/posts/the-ai-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/posts/the-ai-summer/</guid>
      <description>Meta LLaMA, Stanford Alpaca, PaLM, OpenAI GPT-4.
This week has been crazy. The previous week started with the storming LLaMA release from the Meta which advanced to weight leaks on the torrent. Then Stanford released the Alpaca model fine tuned from the LLaMA 7B model on 52K instruction-following demonstrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello, World
#include &amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt; using namespace std; int main() { cout &amp;lt;&amp;lt; &amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34; &amp;lt;&amp;lt; endl; return 0; } </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today I Learned</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/til/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/til/</guid>
      <description>Whatever I end up learning on my day to day exploration. If it seem interesting to me I will share it as a post here.
2025 The SQLite codebase is spread out into several files, but for building they combine all of the source code into a single .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uses this</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/uses/</guid>
      <description>Hardware, services and tools I am using to get things done.
Starting with my dream setup which I found on r/battlestations. I would like to have a similar setup in the coming years for me.
Dream Setup My Current Setup looks something like this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookshelf</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/bookshelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 11:06:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/bookshelf/</guid>
      <description>This will be interesting to some people, who want to read some great books and don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start from. I will try to have these books in physical form and I&amp;rsquo;ll keep updating this list as I read more books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 11:06:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/about/</guid>
      <description>ipa nezubn /nɛzʌb/ &amp;mdash; no meaning, i made it up
an engineer, and a polymath
Hi, I am Ankit aka (nezubn) and I have been working in the field of Machine Learning and Engineering for almost ~5 years. I like reading, building things, where things could be anything between a mobile application, an ml system, a compiler, an operating system, writing kernels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 11:06:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/now/</guid>
      <description>What I am doing now? Work I am working as a Machine Learning Engineer in a startup, OnionDev Tech (Gramvaani). My work involves around writing Django Apps to training and deploying Machine Learning models.
Previous project: To make a QnA System from unstructured data where a farmer can ask anything about his/her crops over an IVR system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://nezubn.com/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 11:06:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nezubn.com/people/</guid>
      <description>
Internet people who write about a variety of topics. I have tried to make this list of people sorted based on their expertise in their respective fields.
Startups, Products &amp;amp; Strategy Balaji Srinivasan | balajis Paul Graham | paulg Aaron Swartz Vitalik Buterin | vitalikbuterin Naval | naval Software Engineering John Siracusa | siracusa Joel Spolsky | spolsky Machine Learning Andrej Karpathy | blog | karpathy Greg Brockman | gdb Yann LeCun | ylecun </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
